It's Miyona, isn't it?
ミヨナさんですよね
Hello, nice to meet you.
こんにちは、初めまして
That's what I was applying for.
応募していたものです
Thank you for contacting me today.
ありがとうございます、今日連絡いただいて
you're welcome.
こちらこそ
It's no different from the photo.
写真と全然変わらないですね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
So cute.
めっちゃ可愛い
Do you usually receive applications like this?
普段こういう応募とか受けたりとかするんですか?
This is how we met.
こうやって会ったりとか
How many times?
何回か
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's cold today.
今日寒いね
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いですね
Amazing clothes.
すごい服が
It looks really warm.
すごい暖かそう
The outerwear is cute, isn't it?
アウター可愛いですよね
That's right.
そうなんですよ
white.
白
It goes great with this bag.
すごいバッグと似合ってて
wonderful.
素晴らしい
So amazing.
すごい素晴らしい
It's around the place.
場所そこら辺にある
It's pretty close, so let's go.
結構近くにあるから、じゃあ行こうか
What were you doing during the day today?
今日は昼間は何してたの?
I was wandering around this afternoon.
今日昼間はゴロゴロしてました
Were you rolling around?
ゴロゴロしてたの?
Didn't you do anything today?
今日何もしてなかったの?
I agree.
そうですね
That's what I did.
そうやったんだ
Do you usually come around there?
普段はそこら辺とか来たりとかする?
It may not come often.
あんまり来ないかもしれないです
That's right.
そうなんだ
Stand there.
そこ立ってね
I don't usually come around here.
普段はここら辺来ないんだ
I agree.
そうですね
Did you get lost?
道迷わなかった?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
Just a little bit?
ちょっとだけ?
yes.
はい
That's right.
そっかそっか
I don't really have a sense of direction.
結構方向音痴ではない
I worked hard on that too.
あれも頑張ってきました
That's right.
そっかそっか
Good, good.
よかったよかった
Aren't your feet cold?
足寒くない?
I'm still holding on.
まだ耐えてる
My child is in trouble.
俺の子大変だよ
In a battle against the cold.
寒さとの勝負で
Fashionable.
おしゃれ
He's extremely tone deaf.
すごい音痴だ
That's a lot to say, isn't it?
めっちゃ言われるでしょ?
Isn't it a waste?
ボテるでしょ?
not at all.
全然
Really?
本当に?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏とかはいないんですか?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいないですね
The foundation is high.
基礎が高い
No, but that's not the case.
いやでもそんなことない
What kind of people are expensive?
どんな人が高い?
I really like people who are kind.
本当にとにかく優しい人がいいです
I want to be pampered.
甘やかされたいです
甘やかされたい
But on the contrary, it seems kind of sweet.
でもなんか逆に甘やかしそうですよね
Ah, but I think it's a Tsukusu type.
ああでもツクス系タイプだと思います
Tux type?
ツ クスタイプ?
yes.
はい
If I were to be used by such a cute girl...
こんな可愛い子につかされたらもう...
You must be happy.
幸せだろうな
Well, what were you doing with this car today?
まあ今日は、この車で何してたの?
I was rolling around today.
今日はゴロゴロしてました
I was relaxing.
ゆっくりしてました
Were you rolling around?
ゴロゴロしてたの?
yes.
はい
Have you been sleeping the whole time?
ずっと寝てたの?
Was there something going on there too?
そこもなんかゴロゴロしてたの?
Were you doing something?
何かやってたの?
I was looking at my phone and playing games.
携帯見たりゲームしたりしてました
Do you play a lot of games?
ゲームは結構してるの?
I'll make a switch.
スイッチとかします
Did you switch with your pet today?
今日はペットでスイッチしたの?
I did.
しました
Are you good at games?
ゲーム得意?
I'm not good at it, but I like it.
得意ではないけど好きです
How many books do you have at home?
家に何本ぐらいあるの?
There are quite a few.
結構あるんですね
I'm putting in a lot of things.
いろいろ入れてます
Switch is interesting.
スイッチ面白いよね
Yes, it's interesting.
はい、 面白いです
What kind of movies are they?
映画とかってどんなの?
Beauty etc.
美容系とか
It's cute to see beauty stuff.
美容系見るのかわいいもんね
I'm learning a lot of things like that.
いろいろそういうの勉強してます
It'll become even cuter.
さらに可愛くなっちゃうんだ
That's already Chikomari.
それはもう、ちこまり
It's getting too cute.
可愛くなりすぎて
Lately, I've been watching some beauty videos.
最近なんか、美容系の動画見てて、
This one is from Preator.
これ、プリエーターのものがある
Yeah, but I wonder what it is.
えー、でもなんだろう
Like the Korean brand Koshime.
韓国のブランドのコシメとか
I see.
なるほどね
It's pretty good.
結構いいです
There's a lot of great Mank brands going on right now.
マンク系って今すごいブランドやってるもんね
yes.
はい
It'll be there soon.
もうそろそろでつくからね
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
Sorry for making you walk.
ごめんね、歩かしちゃって
Yes, it's totally fine.
はい、全然大丈夫です
It's straight here.
ここまっすぐだから
Ah, I see.
あ、わかりました
Once again, Miyona-san.
改めて、みよなさん
yes.
はい
Thank you for today.
今日ありがとうございます
thank you.
ありがとうございます
How old are you now?
今って、歳いくつなんですか?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
I'm young.
私、若いね
When I met you, I thought you were really young.
なんか、会ったときめっちゃ若いなって思って
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Hey.
へー
If I do that now, will you be a student?
今、そうしたら学生さん?
He's a student.
学生ですね
A student.
学生さんが
Do you usually work part-time?
普段はアルバイトとかはしてる?
I usually work at Men's.
普段はメンスで働いてて
Seriously?
マジで?
It's men's.
メンズですって
With mens?
メンスで?
yes.
はい
Hey.
へー
Do you see cute girls like this when you go to men's?
メンズ行ったらこんな可愛い子出てくるの?
It's heaven.
天国じゃん
Hey, that's nice.
へ ー、いいなー
So, if we meet again next time,
だからさ、 次もしまた会ってくれるんだったら、
I want you to do something men's.
メンズ的なことしてほしいな
Oh, not at all.
ああ、全然
Yeah, okay?
ええ、いいの?
yes.
はい
Seriously?
マジで?
I was just saying that I've met like this a few times before.
なんかさ、さっきさ、 何回かこんな感じで会ったことあるって言
It was.
った じゃん
I wish the people I've met a few times would like me to do something men's.
何回か会った人たちもメンズ的なことしてほしいとかならな
Was it?
かった?
No, it wasn't.
いや、 なかったですね
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジで?
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Hey.
へー
If this were the case, I would definitely order it.
これだったら絶対頼んじゃうけどね
By the way, I was recruiting this time.
ちなみに、 今回募集してたじゃん、
It's like an engineering part-time job.
工学バイトみたいな感じで
yes.
はい
So, what's the reason you came?
それでさ、来てくれた理由とかって何?
Huh, why?
え、理由?
Did you want money?
お金が欲しかった?
I wanted an allowance.
おこづかい欲しかった
Spend money.
おこづかい
Mace isn't enough?
メースだけじゃ足りないの?
Well, that's right.
えー、そうですね
Hey.
へー
What are you going to spend the money on?
何使うの、お金?
I really like traveling and all kinds of things,
結構、いろいろ旅行とかも好きなんで、
I spend a lot of money on things like traveling and beauty treatments.
旅行行ったり、美容とかにもお金かかってます
Beauty and travel?
美容と旅行?
yes.
はい
Hey, but I'm sure Mace will be popular, too.
へー、でもさ、メースでもさ、絶対人気あるだろうね、
difference.
さ
I wish I could go to a part-time job like this,
こんなバイトまで行っちゃったらさ、
You can't travel anywhere.
どこにでも旅行行けんじゃん
surely.
確かに
I guess I'm going to space or something.
なんか宇宙とか行っちゃうんだよね
universe.
宇宙
That's about it, isn't it?
それぐらいなんかもう、あれだよね、
Sounds like you'll make money.
稼げそうだよね
Mace is also very popular, right?
メースでもすごい人気なんじゃない?
Well, I'm doing my best.
えー、頑張ってます
Are you working hard?
頑張ってます?
yes.
はい
nice.
いいね
By the way, you said earlier that you met several times.
ちなみに、前の、何回か会ったって言ったじゃん
yes.
はい
What did you do with the person you met last time?
前会った人とは、どんなことした?
It felt pretty normal.
わりと普通なノーマルめな感じでした
Does it feel normal?
ノーマルめな感じ?
yes.
はい
A normal tea party?
ノーマルめなお茶会?
A few things.
ちょっと、いろいろ
A little bit of variety?
ちょっといろいろ?
I did a lot of things.
いろいろしました
Did you do a lot?
いろいろしたの?
yes.
はい
Well, what impressed you the most?
え、一番印象に残ってることは?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
Ah, but there were multiple people.
あ、 でも、複数人したんで
Did more than one person do it?
複数人した?
yes.
はい
Tea party with multiple people?
複数人とお茶会?
That's right, a tea party with multiple people.
そうだね、複数人とお茶会
Tea party.
お茶会
Hey, it was my first time.
ちょっと、初めてだったんで
first time?
初めて?
That's right.
そうなんだ
What if there were multiple people?
複数人としたらどうだった?
Ah, but I was a little scared at first.
あ、でも、ちょっと最初は怖かったんですけど、
It was fun.
楽しかったです
楽しかったんだ
Surprisingly, yes.
意外と、はい
Eh.
えー
Wow, it feels so clean.
すごい、なんか清楚な感じなのに
It's quite naughty.
結構、エッチなんだね
By the way, do you usually enjoy traveling?
ちなみにさ、なんか、普段、旅行が趣味なの?
Do you have any other hobbies or do you like them?
他にいたが趣味だったりとか、好きなの?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
I have a dog, so I like playing with him.
ワンちゃん飼ってるんで、 ワンちゃんと遊んだりするのが好き
is.
です
I also like animals.
動 物がも好きです
Ah, nice.
あー、いいね
I love animals.
動物好きなの
Children who love animals are already kind, even Darin.
動物好きな子ってもう、 ダリンでも優しそうだよね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Yeah.
うん
Wow, it looks like he's going to do some self-indulgence.
すごい、なんか、放肆してくれそう
So, after all, it wasn't more than S.
それで、やっぱり、あれは、 Sよりではなくて、
From M?
Mより?
That's right.
ですね
M?
That's right.
そうなんだね
After all, I hear that many children who like animals are masochistic.
やっぱり動物好きな子はね、 Mな子が多いって聞くからね
That's right.
そうなんだね
Wow, that's great, listen.
すごい、よくね、聞く
Even my friends have said this before.
これまで友達も言ってた
By the way, how many cup breasts are there?
ちなみにさ、 おっぱいってさ、何カップだ?
About C cup.
Cカップくらい
Oh, that's strange.
おー、微妙だね
You have fair skin.
肌白いもんね
Ah, but that's true.
あー、でも確かに言われますね
I feel very beautiful because my skin is white.
肌白いから、すごい綺麗な感じする
Her nipples are amazing, so beautiful.
なんか、乳首とかもすごい、めっちゃ綺麗だ
By the way, what kind of underwear do you wear today?
ちなみに、 下着の、今日の下着はどんな感じですか?
Today it's red.
今日は赤色です
red?
赤色?
Just for a moment, can I have a look?
ちょっとだけさ、 見せてもらってもいい?
Wow, it matches the scent.
すごい、香りに合わせて
By the way, I'm wearing underwear.
ちなみに下着つけてる
Ah, I saw it.
あ、見えちゃった
I could see it.
見えちゃった
By the way, what's below?
ちなみにさ、 下は?
You can see the bottom, so it becomes pants.
下は、見えるから、 ズボンになっちゃうから
That's what it feels like.
そういう感じなんだ
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
A lot of kids these days are like that.
最近の子も多いよね、そういう
The pants are together.
一緒になってる、ズボン
By the way, where do you feel it?
ちなみにさ、 どこが感じる?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Breasts and chestnuts.
おっぱいと、 栗
おっぱいと栗
What will you do?
どうされるんですか?
I like being attacked gently.
優しく攻められるのが好きです
gently?
優しく?
Both?
どっちも?
Both.
どっちも
That's right.
そうなんだ
Amazing teeth pulling.
すごい歯引き
Aren't you standing there a little?
少し立ってんじゃない?
child
こ
It's getting a little damp too.
っち もちょっと湿ってきてる
It's getting really wet.
すっごい湿ってきてる
It's so beautiful.
すっごい綺麗なんだ
Do you like having your breasts touched?
おっぱいとは触られるのが好き?
Turn around and look like there's no one there.
後ろ向いて、 やつないみたいな
What do women usually do?
普段さ、 女人とかってどうしてるの?
Like a phone.
電話とか
A phone?
電話とか?
Do you use toys?
おもちゃ使うの?
Yeah.
うん
Let's try it out.
さあ、使ってみよう
Yeah.
うん
Looks like I'm going.
行きそう
Did you just go?
今、行っちゃったの?
Your phone is weak.
電話弱いんだね
You should go further.
もっと行っていいんだよ
Yeah.
うん
People often say that my pussy is beautiful.
マンコキ綺麗ってよく言われるでしょ
Yeah.
うん
What about your child?
さまの子は?
Sama appears and becomes Sama.
さまが出てさまになるのさ
Add it a little deeper.
もうちょっと奥まで加えて
It's about time, yeah.
そろそろさ、 うん
I wanted to sleep.
寝たくなっちゃった
Yeah.
うん
Can I sleep?
寝てもいい?
Yeah.
うん
Oh, it feels so good.
ああ、気持ちいい
I think I'll go too.
俺も行きそう
I won't go.
行かない
I'll put it inside.
中に出すよ
Next time, let's play Maze again.
次はさ、 またメイズプレイしようよ